https://easydns.com/privacy-policy?icode=parked_page

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footer+ .app, .guru, .co, .io, .us, .rocks and more... easyDNS™ does not in any way share the personal information that you have included in the personal information section of your easyDNS™ member pages. Your information is neither sold nor rented to any third party or information collection organization and is used solely for the administration of your easyDNS™ account.Your easyDNS™ membership information:The information collected by easyDNS™, including name, address, company name, email address, phone number and fax number, is used to validate the authenticity of requests made by individuals or organizations with respect to information contained in their easyDNS™ account, or in response to a lost password or lost user ID issue. We may also use the information to contact members with important system or account information, changes to services, and other important easyDNS™ updates. With the members permission we may also use the information to provide updates on new services and other special announcements.The answers supplied to the secret questions selected during the sign up process may be used in concert with personal email addresses and phone numbers to assist easyDNS™ members in the generation of new passwords during the automated password recovery process. The questions and answer pairs may also be used by easyDNS™ support staff to authenticate various requests by our members made directly via email and telephone.Personal information that exists within an easyDNS™ account will remain active until the member has requested that the account be deleted or until the account and the information contained within has been deleted during the routine deletion of dormant and unused easyDNS™ member accounts.Public Whois information:All registered domain names are required by ICANN to contain accurate, publicly accessible whois information including the names, address and telephone numbers of all listed contacts.easyDNS members may choose to use their personal information as the public whois information for domain names registered with easyDNS™. However, whois information is not private information and cannot be protected by easyDNS under this privacy policy.For an example of what Whois information looks like please visit easyWhois™ and perform a Whois lookup on “easyDNS.com”.If you have any questions or concerns please contact privacy@easydns.comEuropean General Data Protection RuleseasyDNS is a Canadian entity, incorporated in the Province of Ontario. As such we conform to PIPEDA, the privacy regulation of our home country. For domains who registrant address resides within member countries of the EU subject to the GDPR we are currently redacting persona; data fields for whois records under .COM and .NET. For all other TLDs we are following the lead of our registry backend provider, OpenHRS – which is currently redacting personal fields across all whois lookups.Our Use of CookiesWe do not collect personal information without your knowledge and permission, nor do we resell or distribute any site visitor data, including information that may be collected as a natural by-product of your visit.For general information on what cookies are and what they can and can’t do for you, take a quick look at our Cookie FAQ below.The widespread concern about cookies has very little to do with the technology and very much to do with the fear that unscrupulous site operators might use cookies for unacceptable practices.easyDNS™ only uses cookies to remember certain things about you between visits to our site, and as you move between pages on the site.Our Web site utilizes cookies in order to provide you with a better experience. For security reasons (even though only we can read the cookies we send you), easyDNS™ will only store a unique identifying number in the cookie we send. We never store your username, password, credit card information, or any other personal information about you in our cookie.Cookie FAQWhat is a cookie?A cookie is a very small text file placed on your hard drive by a website.Why use cookies?Cookies are the easiest way to tell the website you are visiting that you have returned. They also provide a way to store information about you between visits.Are they harmful?No. Here are a list of things that a cookie can’t do:it can’t deliver viruses to your computerit can’t be read by any website other than the one that gave it to youit can’t allow us to read files or sensitive information on your hard driveit can’t reveal personal information about yourself, where you live, what your income is, or any other piece of personal information that you don’t explicitly providePrimary Sidebar#AxisOfEasySign up for our weekly newsletter SubscribeSearch BlogSearch this websiteWhat Are You Waiting For?Get easyDNS on your side and move your domains or DNS today.Transfer a domainRegister a new domainGet anycast DNSRecent Posts [AxisOfEasy] Secrecy Around Top Canadian Cyber-Security Intelligence Officer Caught Spying For China [AxisOfEasy] Drupal Deploys Emergency Fix For Critical Vulnerability [AxisOfEasy] Hackers Target Crypto Exchanges Via Their Domain Registrar [AxisOfEasy] Ticketmaster To Require Immunity Passports For Event Attendance [AxisOfEasy] Police Pilot Program Will Live Stream Neighbourhood Ring Cameras [AxisOfEasy]
Drop What You’re Doing AGAIN And Upgrade Chrome AGAIN Webmail update at web.easymail.caNetwork StatusView Current Network StatusNew Knowledge BaseManaging Mission Critical Domains & DNS: The Book
We literally wrote the book on this stuff, Learn more.Categories#AxisOfEasyAlertsAvis aux membersCustomer-centrismHelp and SupportHowto's and HelpIn BetaIndustry WatchJobsMember MailoutsMetaviewsNewsOf InterestResolvedstatusTakedowns and ShakedownsTips and TricksUncategorizedUpdatedUsing URLs Effectivelyvia DomainHELP.comWhat's NewWho Uses easyDNS?FootereasyDNS Technologies, Inc. Founded In 19984243C Dundas St. W, Suite 405 Etobicoke, ON M8X 1Y3Phone: +1.855.321.EASY (3279)Fax: +1.647.438.6227support@easydns.comProducts & ServicesDomain NamesDNSWeb HostingEmail HostingSSL Certificates & TrustSupport/HelpPhone +1.855.321.EASY (3279)ContactKnowledge BaseResources & Tools#AxisOfEasyAbout easyDNSBlogOur GuaranteeEmail HostingWeb Hosting
